<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software on Pantrypoints</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software on Pantrypoints</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/docs/tech/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GPL vs MIT vs Apache vs BSD vs LGPL</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/software/licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/software/licenses/</guid>
      <description>GPL (General Public License): Copyleft: Requires derivative works (modified versions) to be released under the same GPL license. Focus: Encourages open-source development and collaboration. Restrictions: May not be ideal for commercial usage as it could require releasing your entire product as open-source.&#xA;Example: Linux kernel.&#xA;MIT License: Permissive: Allows users to use, modify, and distribute the software freely, including for commercial purposes. Focus: Provides flexibility and promotes wider adoption. Restrictions: Few restrictions, but contributors do not have to contribute back their modifications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Methodology</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/software/methodology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/software/methodology/</guid>
      <description>After the SRS is finalized the methodology to make the software is next chosen.&#xA;Waterfall This is the most traditional project management methodology. It comprises a series of stages executed consecutively. From conceptualization through construction, implementation, and maintenance, each phase flows down to the next.&#xA;Waterfall places a strong emphasis on planning. Before starting any software project, teams must determine their goals, cost estimates, timelines, and resources. Team members must also know their roles and responsibilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is requirement analysis in software engineering?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/software/requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/software/requirements/</guid>
      <description>Requirement analysis is the first step of the software development process and software development life cycle (SDLC).&#xA;It is understanding what software is supposed to do and the constraints it must operate within.&#xA;It is usually a technical process and a team effort where stakeholders and software developers determine the needs and conditions that a software product must meet.&#xA;This process involves identifying, documenting, and analyzing these business requirements to ensure that they are clearly understood and feasible.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
