<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Resources on Pantrypoints</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Resources on Pantrypoints</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Download Youtube Videos</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/download-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/download-youtube/</guid>
      <description>There are 3 general ways to get Youtube videos:&#xA;Through Youtube App Through Web-based Downloaders Through Screencast recordings Youtube App This lets you download the video in low or mid quality format, and watch the video offline.&#xA;Pros:&#xA;No ads or popups Cons:&#xA;You have to connect to the internet every few days. If the video or channel is taken down, then the video also disappears from your app This is the major disadvantage and is why you have to abandon this method Screencast Recordings You can record the video through screen recorder apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Status Codes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/http/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/http/</guid>
      <description>Status codes are a 3-digit integer code giving the result of the attempt to understand and satisfy the request.&#xA;Classes The first digit of the status-code defines the class of response. The last two digits do not have any categorization role. There are 5 values for the first digit:&#xA;Common 1xx code reason description spec 1xx Informational &amp;ldquo;indicates an interim response for communicating connection status or request progress prior to completing the requested action and sending a final response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) vs URL (Uniform Resource Locator)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/uri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/uri/</guid>
      <description>. URI URL Scope Can be used outside of internet Use for internet only HTTP, HTTPS, or FTP Examples urn:isbn:0-302-38006-X (identifies a book by its ISBN)mailto:john.doe@example.com (identifies an email address)file:///path/to/file.txt (identifies a local file) ftp://ftp.example.com/public/file.zip (file download location) All URLs are URIs, but not all URIs are URLs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Useful Free Tools for Web Development 2021</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/useful-free-tools-web-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/useful-free-tools-web-development/</guid>
      <description>Here are some free online tools that we use to develop our own app and websites. I&amp;rsquo;ve put up this list for my own use in case I have to scrub data using a different computer, like the ones in internet cafes&#xA;Machine Learning Tool Purpose Google Colab Free online machine learning environment Graphics Resources Purpose Cloudinary Free Image, Video, File Hosting. Has a faster CDN than Kraken or Sirv Sirv Free Image, Video, File Hosting Canva Makes infographics Google Slides Makes basic graphics, has offline mode Lucidcharts Makes graphs Undraw Free Images Unsplash Free Graphics / Illustrations / Photos Video Resources Purpose Openshot Free video editor Pexels Free Images and Stock Videos Hosting Resources Purpose Netlify Web App Hosting, Free limited static sites Render Web App Hosting, Free limited static sites Github Pages Free limited static sites Gitlab Pages Free limited static sites Cloudflare Content Deliver Network Heroku Deploy web servers (needs credit card) Gigalixir Similar to Heroku but doesn&amp;rsquo;t need a credit card Google Cloud Platform Deploy web servers (needs credit card), has free trial Web Tools Purpose Observatory Scan your website for vulnerabilities SSL Test Check your SSL Open Ports check which ports are open Map Tools Purpose Lat Long Finder Latitude and Longitude Finder based on Address data (Faster than Google Maps) Text Tools Purpose Remove Line Breaks remove line breaks in text Word to HTML convert Word to HTML Remove Letter Accents Useful for non-english text ERB to Slim HTML to slim converter for Ruby templates Site Performance Tools Purpose Load Impact and Loader Stress-test your site Pingdom Test Check site&amp;rsquo;s load speed Nibbler Check your site&amp;rsquo;s performance Page Insights Check site performance SEO Tools Purpose Ahrefs Check broken links, domain authority, keywords, etc Broken Link Checker Ubersuggest Find keywords for your content Moz Check basic SEO Semrush Site Audit Social Tools Purpose Facebook Adds social buttons, check open graph tags </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Hotlink Images from Google Drive and Dropbox</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/hotlink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/web/hotlink/</guid>
      <description>In order to keep the Pantrypoints app resilient, it does not use image hosting which would increase the system&amp;rsquo;s cost and reduce maintainability. Instead, we use hotlinking which shows images hosted by other websites and apps.&#xA;There are generally two kinds of hosting services for image:&#xA;1. File hosting These host files for storage purposes. Examples are:&#xA;Google Drive Dropbox 2. Image hosting These host images and video for serving over the internet, usually through a CDN (content delivery network).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
