<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hackathons on Pantrypoints</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/hackathons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hackathons on Pantrypoints</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/hackathons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pantrypoints @ Enhack 2023</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/23-07-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/23-07-01/</guid>
      <description>We pitched Pantrypoints Build and Rewards at Enhack 2023, as Static Sites and Rewards, respectively.&#xA;Enhack 2023 is a hackathon by Enstack, an ecommerce app based in the Philippines.&#xA;We used Canva to make the deck for the first time. Canva has a quirk that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t make links automatically. This prevented us from easily linking a demo of our online app during the pitch.&#xA;We didn&amp;rsquo;t win as they were looking for an AI product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximized Farming @ Packethacks 2023</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/23-06-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/23-06-03/</guid>
      <description>We submitted our Maximized Farming System to Packethacks 2023 , an IoT Hackathon, and made it as one of the 32 semifinalists.&#xA;The Packethacks will be held in the Packetworx event in the World Trade Center.&#xA;Unfortunately, we didn&amp;rsquo;t make it to the finals, which were made up of the followng teams:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diet-Disease Reference @ FLExPHD</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/23-04-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/23-04-28/</guid>
      <description>We made it into the Top 40 of the FLExPHD competition with our app Diet-Disease Reference , as part of Pantrypoints Health.&#xA;graphics/diet.jpg&#xA;Diet-Disease Reference is a food reference app that promotes the use of food for medicine and nutrition, as &amp;rsquo;nutraceuticals&#39;.&#xA;It aims to drive demand for a planetary health diet which is composed mostly of plant-based food. Our main innovations are:&#xA;the linking of diseases to nutrients and to the food that has them the use of machine learning to make adding content faster The linking of diseases to nutrients uses the paradigm of alternative medicine, namely:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pantrypoints Circle for the ADB Visualizing Climate Change &amp; Resilience Challenge</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/22-11-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/22-11-08/</guid>
      <description>Pantrypoints Circle is our proposed system that implements a circular economy by embracing global warming, with its disasters.&#xA;Its first implementation is called Village Contract Farming (VCF). In the Philippines, we will implement this VCF as &amp;ldquo;Basurayuda&amp;rdquo;, which is a program that mobilizes unemployed people to collect plastic waste and kitchen waste to be recycled and turned into compost.&#xA;This system relies on communities and moneyless systems in order to create a &amp;ldquo;common economy&amp;rdquo; powered by &amp;ldquo;common interest&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pantrypoints World @ Web3 Hackathon</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/22-10-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/22-10-30/</guid>
      <description>We put up our Pantrypoints Coins prototype for the upcoming Web3 Hackathon.&#xA;Update We didn&amp;rsquo;t make it to the Top 10. Some of the top teams were:&#xA;Team Xcalp Webmint FRM Coin Team Dvcode Sheesh! Team Life We learned that the play to earn model does not work for the app maker because there must be another source of revenue like ads, subscription, esports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superphysics @ the 3rd PNP Hackathon</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/22-10-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/22-10-15/</guid>
      <description>We signed up for the 3rd PNP Hackathon to take on the Predictive Policing Challenge.&#xA;PNP Hackathon We&amp;rsquo;ve been working on Pantrypoints for most of the year without doing much for ISAIAH, which is the machine learning part of the Superphysics system. So we joined the hackathon to develop the predictive analyis part, which we will call &amp;ldquo;Criminality Prediction System (CPS)&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;The system uses palm prints to predict a person&amp;rsquo;s tendency for criminal behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pantrypoints @ Hack4Food</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/22-03-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/22-03-22/</guid>
      <description>We joined Hack4Food to pitch Pantrypoints.&#xA;We didn&amp;rsquo;t win and so we decided to split our system into a Pantrypoints platform, and a private ERP-ish app called Pantrypreneur.&#xA;Unlike Pantrypoints that uses donation points, trade points, etc., Pantrypreneur only uses loyalty points. This manifests as a loyalty app or customer rewards system.&#xA;Ideally, our system should&amp;rsquo;ve been deployed by 2018 since our model predicted a stagflation starting in Q1 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pantrypoints @ Fishackathon</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/22-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/22-02-01/</guid>
      <description>We submitted our entry to the Fishackathon 2022 as Pantry Points.&#xA;The system is inspired by the Inca empire which used granaries as qullqa and non-monetary valuation as quipu to circulate resources. Such a system was praised by Adam Smith for being more sustainable than the precious-metals-based system of the Spanish.&#xA;The Fishackathon is organized by Each Mile and Padang &amp;amp; Co&#xA;Updates Date . March 2022 We made it to the finals but didn&amp;rsquo;t make the top 3 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pantry Govern @ Impacthub Smart Cities</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/21-12-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/21-12-11/</guid>
      <description>We joined Impacthub Smart Cities to pitch the last part of the Pantry system &amp;ndash; Pantry Govern.&#xA;From the event, we were able finalize the features :&#xA;Permit and Issue tracking Local transportation routes map Local News (as Pantry Beacon) This completes all the platforms and features of the Pantry system. Because we didn&amp;rsquo;t get support back in 2016, development progressed very slowly. It came too late for the crisis that we predicted in 2019 which turned out to be Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moneyless Banking @ Impacthub 2050</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/21-10-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/21-10-09/</guid>
      <description>We made it to the Top 10 of the Impacthub Agriculture Challenge but didn&amp;rsquo;t make it to the Top 3.&#xA;Most of the challenges were agriculture related:&#xA;How can tech give real-time access to prices and supply of vegetables? How can small farmholders who have no tech, no money, and are illiterate better manage their farm operations to increase yields and profits? How can farm tourism thrive with real-time information on carrying capacity?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle @ Plastics Hackathon of the UN Habitat</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/21-06-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/21-06-05/</guid>
      <description>The recent community pantry phenomenon has inspired us to overhaul &amp;lsquo;SORA&amp;rsquo; into &amp;lsquo;Pantrypoints Economy-as-a-Service (EaaS)&amp;rsquo; to emphasize the decentralized and hyperlocal nature of our proposed economic system.&#xA;SORA will now be EaaS which is split into 3 independent parts:&#xA;Pantrypoints Pantrypreneur ISAIAH Those parts will have the SORA features :&#xA;Old New SORA Govern or City Pantrypoints City SORA Trade Pantrypoints World SORA Health Pantrypoints Health SORA Agreeculture Pantrypreneur Farm SORA Apprentice Pantrypoints Educate SORA Reuse and SORA Relief Pantrypoints Circle SORA Beacon Pantrypoints Build We entered Pantrypoints Circle in the 3R Plastics Hackathon of the UN-Habitat in the Philippines and made it to the preliminary round, but didn&amp;rsquo;t make it to the Top 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zalo Hackathon</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/17-11-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/17-11-16/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re at the Zalo hackathon with Henry and Vin as Team Happy City.&#xA;Zalo is a Vietnamese messaging app that is headquartered in HCM city.&#xA;We tried out integrating a recommendation system for SORA using backend technologies. We&amp;rsquo;re not experts in recommendation systems and so we didn&amp;rsquo;t make any place.&#xA;Updates Date . December 12, 2021 Our recommendation system eventually became ISAIAH Match while the name &amp;lsquo;Happy City&amp;rsquo; led to the name &amp;lsquo;Pantrypoints City&amp;rsquo;&amp;quot; </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup Weekend Cambodia</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/17-02-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/17-02-05/</guid>
      <description>We made it to the semifinals of Startup Weekend Cambodia pitching DCS (Debt Clearing System)!&#xA;Startup Weekend is a 54-hour startup hackathon and pitching competition held in various countries, organized by Techstars. The Cambodia event focuses on fintech solutions and is sponsored by ABA Bank of Cambodia.&#xA;Updates Date . Nov 2020 DCS evolved to become Resource Banking of Adam Smith Nov 2021 Resource Banking changed into Points Banking to avoid any theoretical connection with the Marxist Resource-based economy </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NARA @ NASA Space Apps Challenge 2016</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/16-01-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/16-01-10/</guid>
      <description>We got accepted into the NASA Space apps challenge in Saigon!&#xA;Our entry is NARA or Non-Arbitrary Resource Allocation:&#xA;https://2016.spaceappschallenge.org/challenges/earth/emobile-pastoralism/projects/social-resource-allocation-sora It focuses on pastoralism for African countries like Malawi. We deployed it on Heroku.&#xA;Updates Date . December 12, 2021 NARA evolved to become SORA to focus on the social network feature, which then evolved into Pantrypoints to focus on the Points feature to implement the Effort Theory of Value </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NARA @ Hatch 2015</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/15-10-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/15-10-24/</guid>
      <description>We had a booth in Hatch 2015 as NARA or Non-Arbitrary Resource Allocation under Team Elements.&#xA;Hatch is an incubator in Hanoi Vietnam that has its own coworking site. We learned of the event after participating in the Hack for Social Good held by the United Nations Development Program and the British Council.&#xA;Notable startups in the event were Abivn.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
