<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Training Resources on Pantrypoints</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Training Resources on Pantrypoints</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>9 CBT Areas</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/9-areas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/9-areas/</guid>
      <description>1. Practical work area Where the trainee acquires the skills and knowledge components of the competencies prescribed by the standard.&#xA;2. Learning Resource Center Area that provides the trainee with the knowledge requirements in the various modules responding to the competencies.&#xA;3. Institutional Assessment Area Where recognition of prior learning is done by the trainer.&#xA;Upon completion of all modules within a competency, the trainee is handed a Certificate of Achievement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COC2 Script</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/script-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/script-1/</guid>
      <description>Before Assessment: Establish The Context And Purpose Of Assessment + Do The Evidence Gathering Process Script What To Do Document/S Needed I will check: Materials / Tools Check the Assessment Package Inspect the docs Attendance Sheet, Application Form During Assessment: Prepare the Candidate Script What To Do Document/S Needed Introduce yourself Wear ID ID &amp;ldquo;Please submit admission slip&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Please sign attendance sheet&amp;rdquo; Counter check signatures Attendance Sheet Admission Slip &amp;ldquo;Here is your Application Form&amp;rdquo; Show Application form and SAG Application form SAG &amp;ldquo;Today I will conduct Web Dev NCIII.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication and Effective Questioning</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/communication/</guid>
      <description>Communication is the transfer of information.&#xA;4 principles of Osgood Schramm Model of Communication Circular Communication not linear Equal and reciprocal Communication Messages require interpretation 3 steps for communicating: encoding, decoding and interpreting. There are 2 parties:&#xA;The sender (origin encoder) The receiver (decodes and interprets). Types of Messages Verbal messages - words Non-verbal - body language, lights, sounds, pictures and symbols, etc. One way and Two way Communication Sending a message is one-way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Competency Based Curriculum</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/course/</guid>
      <description>The Competency Based Curriculum is a plan for structured series of learning experiences toward achieving of competencies identified by the industry; it details training methodologies, resources, facilities, infrastructure and other materials required both for training and assessment strategies.&#xA;It is a specification of the course a trainee will undertake to attain workplace competencies. It is developed based on the Training Regulations.&#xA;Components of CBC:&#xA;Course Design Module of Instruction Course Title Unit Title Nominal Duration Module Title Qualification Level Course Desc Module Descriptor Entry Reqs Nominal Duration Course Structure Summary of Learning Outcomes Resources Assesment Criteria Assessment Method Contents Course Delivery Condition Trainer&amp;rsquo;s Qualification Assemssement Method is an overall description of the course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotions and Feelings</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/emotions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/emotions/</guid>
      <description>Emotions are instinctive and neurological reactions to a stimulus, creating biochemical and electrical reactions activated through neuro-transmitters and hormones released by the brain (e.g., frightened by a sudden loud noise).&#xA;Emotions are messages to let us know how things are going at the moment. All emotions are useful and helpful. But, sometimes, it is helpful to be able to change the way we are feeling.&#xA;Feelings are mental associations and reactions to an emotion that we assign with a particular meaning, influenced by our personal experiences, temperament, beliefs, memories, and thoughts (e.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus Group Discussion</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/focus/</guid>
      <description>Focus group discussions are used to gain knowledge about a particular topic or need by interviewing a group of people directly affected by the issue. Focus group data can be used to collect information for many purposes, such as conducting a needs assessment or evaluating a program.&#xA;Approaching Focus Group Facilitation&#xA;Two approaches are essential to facilitating focus groups.&#xA;· The first is being a “blank slate.” This means approaching the focus group with an open mind and as few preconceptions as possible about what participants are likely to say or not say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gagne Theory</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/gagne/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/gagne/</guid>
      <description>Robert Gagné, an educational psychologist, created a theory that focuses on how to organize learning experiences for optimal results. It emphasizes:&#xA;the internal processes of learning the external conditions that support those processes. Five Categories of Learning Outcomes There are 5 main things learners can master:&#xA;Intellectual Skills These are cognitive abilities for problem-solving, classifying, and applying rules (e.g., mathematical operations, scientific reasoning).&#xA;Verbal Information Stating organized knowledge (e.g., reciting facts, describing historical events).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learners Learning Objective</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/trainee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/trainee/</guid>
      <description>In CBT, we consider individual differences in training because CBT is self-paced.&#xA;The design of training and instructional materials should suit each trainee.&#xA;CHARACTERISTICS OF LEARNERS One important part of planning a training session is to analyze trainees so that the training suits their:&#xA;Ability level&#xA;learning styles &amp;amp; preferences&#xA;Motivations&#xA;Interests&#xA;because they are the bases in choosing the methodologies to be used by the trainer. It is important to note that:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Observation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/observation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/observation/</guid>
      <description>Observation&#xA;actual evidence gathering soetimes observation is not possible should observe a range of activities supplement with questioning Demonstrations&#xA;showing how to use things Questioning&#xA;evidence gathering provides evidence of knowledge Record answers&#xA;Written test&#xA;assess underpinning knowledge supplement evidence Portfolio&#xA;individual evidence of work outputs over time Portfolio evidence&#xA;these must be valid sufficient current. These must relate to the elements, performance criteria, etc </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occupational Safety and Health</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/health/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/health/</guid>
      <description>Occupational safety and health is a discipline with aims to protect every worker against the dangers of injury, sickness or death through safe and healthful working conditions (OSHC-DOLE, 2016).&#xA;It has 3 interdependent concepts:&#xA;Occupational safety This is the understanding the causes of accidents at work and ways to prevent unsafe act and unsafe conditions in any workplace.&#xA;Safety at work discusses concepts on good housekeeping, proper materials handling and storage, machine safety, electrical safety, fire prevention and control, safety inspection, and accident investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problem Solving</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/problem/</guid>
      <description>Every organization are faced with problems or potential problems. It is important to know your role in the process. There are two important things to remember about problems and conflicts: they happen all the time and they are opportunities to improve the system and the relationships. They are actually providing us with information that we can use to fix what needs fixing and do a better job.&#xA;Defining the Problem These steps will help you clearly identify the root cause of a problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Profession vs. Occupation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/profession/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/profession/</guid>
      <description>Profession Profession is an activity that requires specialized training, knowledge, qualification and skills.&#xA;It usually required qualification for you to be a member of a professional body, and certificate of practice or license.&#xA;This further requires prolonged formal preparation and meets certain higher level criteria that raise it to a level above that of an occupation.&#xA;A certain code of conduct is set up by the respective body of the profession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Script On The Conduct Of Competency Assessment (COC2)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/script-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/script-2/</guid>
      <description>Before Assessment A) Establish The Context And Purpose Of Assessment Check:&#xA;Materials/Supplies Tools &amp;amp; Equipment Documents Needed: Assessment Package&#xA;Specific Instruction to the Candidate Rating Sheets (Demo and Oral Questioning /Interview) Competency Assessment Results Summary Written Test - Multiple choice or True or False Answers Sheet - Written test B) Plan And Prepare The Evidence Gathering Process Check the Assessment Package Check the following&#xA;Attendance Sheet Application Form During Assessment C) Prepare The Candidate Part 1: Introduction My name is (state your name).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Session Plan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/session/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/session/</guid>
      <description>Session [Lesson] Plan is a simply stated, clearly written and flexible trainer aid for conducting a session or module. It is:&#xA;based on the curriculum of the unit of competency accomplished according to the suggested format Benefits of a Session Plan Gives the trainers an idea of where they are and where they are going Gives the trainers and the learners a clear idea of what they are doing Records the training sessions the trainers have taken Gives the trainers a starting point if they have to do the training again with another learner or group of learners Gives the trainers a firm base to review their performance 8 Steps For Designing an Effective Session Plan Define the purpose of the training and target audience Determine participants’ characteristics and training needs Define training goals and objectives Outline training content Develop instructional activities Prepare the written session plan Prepare participants’ evaluation forms Determine follow-up activities for the event Elements Of A Session Plan Industry Sector Qualification Title and Level Unit of Competency Module Title Learning Outcomes Introduction Learning Activities Evaluation Teacher’s Reflection </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skills Versus Competency</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/skills/</guid>
      <description>Name Description Skill A group of tasks performed to a specific level of competency or proficiency Competency | A skill performed to a specific standard under specific conditions.&#xA;Competency Competency involves applying knowledge, skills and attitudes to perform work activities to the standard expected in the workplace.&#xA;Competencies are gained through:&#xA;life experience formal education apprenticeship on-the-job experience self-help programs training and development programs Key features of competency being able to do the job knowing how and why things are done knowing what to do if things go wrong Knowing the right approach to do a job properly and safely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Table of Specifications and Bloom&#39;s Taxonomy</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/table-of-specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/table-of-specifications/</guid>
      <description>The Table of Specifications is used to prepare test questions based on each topic that what was learned.&#xA;It splits up the test items for each topic according to Benjamin Bloom&amp;rsquo;s taxonomy made up of 6 pyramid steps.&#xA;Create Evaluate Analyze Apply Understand Remember Here, we explain the other essentials and basics of a Table of Specifications used in TVET.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teams</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/team/</guid>
      <description>Teamwork is the key factor that makes human work together to achieve common goals.&#xA;Q: contribute to the effectiveness of a team? A: team goals linked to organizational goals&#xA;Teamwork is the effort of group of people with complementary skills who are committed to a common purpose and hold themselves mutually accountable for its achievement. Ideally, the team develops a distinct identity and work together in a co-ordinated and mutually supportive way to fulfil their goal or purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ten Principles of CBT</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/10-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/10-principles/</guid>
      <description>1. The training is based on competency standards. The Competency Standard (CS) is the written specification of the knowledge, skills and attitudes and values required for a job or performance.&#xA;The industry workers identify these standards.&#xA;These are promulgated by the TESDA in the Training Regulations (TR).&#xA;The Competency Based Curriculum (CBC) is derived from the Competency Standards.&#xA;It is a plan for structured learning experiences toward achieving competencies.&#xA;It details:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ten Principles of CBT</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/principles/</guid>
      <description>1. The training is based on competency standards The Competency Standard (CS) is the written specification of the knowledge, skills and attitudes and values required for a job or performance.&#xA;The industry workers identify these standards.&#xA;These are promulgated by the TESDA in the Training Regulations (TR).&#xA;The Competency Based Curriculum (CBC) is derived from the Competency Standards.&#xA;It is a plan for structured learning experiences toward achieving competencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trainer&#39;s Methodology</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/methodology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/methodology/</guid>
      <description>The assessment for Trainer&amp;rsquo;s Methodology is made up of 2 parts:&#xA;Deliver Training Session (COC1) Conduct Competency Assessment (COC2) Code No BASIC COMPETENCIES 500311109 Lead Workplace Communication 500232101 Apply math and science principles in technical training 500232102 Apply environmental principles and advocate conservation 500232103 Utilize IT applications in technical training 500311110 Lead small teams 500232104 Apply work ethics, values and quality principles 500232105 Work effectively in vocational education and training 500232106 Foster and promote a learning culture 500232107 Ensure healthy and safe learning environment 500232108 Maintain and enhance professional practice 500232109 Develop and promote appreciation for cost-benefits of technical training 500232110 Develop and promote global understanding of labor markets Code No CORE COMPETENCIES TVT232301 Plan training sessions TVT232302 Facilitate learning sessions TVT232303 Supervise Work-based learning TVT232304 Conduct competency assessment TVT232305 Maintain training facilities TVT232306 Utilize electronic media in facilitating training COC1: Deliver Training Session (As Trainer) 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Design</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/training/</guid>
      <description>Training design is a systematic process that develops education and training programs.&#xA;Instructional Design, also Instructional Systems Design (ISD) creates &amp;ldquo;instructional experiences which make the acquisition of knowledge and skill more efficient, effective, and appealing.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;It is made up of:&#xA;determining the current state and needs of the learner defining the end goal of instruction creating some &amp;ldquo;intervention&amp;rdquo; to assist in the transition. Ideally, the process is informed by pedagogically (process of teaching) and andragogically (adult learning) tested theories of learning and may take place in student-only, teacher-led or community-based settings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Regulations</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/regulations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/regulations/</guid>
      <description>Training Regulations These are the rules that testing centers and courses must abide by.&#xA;The Training Regulation (TR) is the document for competency assessment and curriculum development for competency-based technical education.&#xA;The Training Regulations has 2 components:&#xA;Occupational skills standard Training standards The Training Regulations serve as basis for the:&#xA;Competency assessment and certification Registration and delivery of training programs Development of curriculum and assessment instruments Every qualification has its own Training Regulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work-Based Training</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/services/training/work/</guid>
      <description>Work-based training assumes that the necessary equipment and machinery are available.&#xA;As trainer, you have to check whether all of which are in place and can be used by the trainees during training.&#xA;It is also important to discover, however, what additional materials will help. Books, pamphlets, diagrams, models may help trainees to develop their knowledge and skills more quickly.&#xA;If the work-based training shall be conducted within the training center, then it is even more important to build the correct range of resources.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
