<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Supereconomics on Pantrypoints</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Supereconomics on Pantrypoints</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What are Social Points?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/social-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/social-points/</guid>
      <description>Pantrypoints uses 4 types of points which represent the 4 prices and the four laws of value :&#xA;Point Type Purpose Example Donation Points nominal value Donations Loyalty Points real value Frequent Purchases Exchange Points market value Barter Investment Points natural value Investing in kind (Equipment, seeds, training, etc) Valuing the Valueless Social points represent the abstract value of anything, under the idea that everything that exists has a value otherwise it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t exist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are Loyalty Points?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/loyalty-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/loyalty-points/</guid>
      <description>Pantrypoints uses four types of points which represent the four prices and the four laws of value :&#xA;Point Type Purpose Example Donation Points nominal value Donations Loyalty Points real value Frequent Purchases Exchange Points market value Barter Investment Points natural value Investing in kind (Equipment, seeds, training, etc) Loyalty Points Loyalty points represent the excess productivity that is owed by the seller to the buyer for sustaining his livelihood (economic svadharma).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are Investment Points?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/investment-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/investment-points/</guid>
      <description>Last week, we were invited to join the SIS Online Hackathon, wherein the organizers were looking for a tech solution for B2B cash management. The Covid pandemic has wreaked havoc on cash and many customers are unable to pay their suppliers.&#xA;Fortunately, our proposed economic system, called Pantrypoints , derived from Adam Smith, is purpose-built to predict and solve such problems. In fact, we have been warning of a huge global economic crisis as early as 2015.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Economy-as-a-Service or EAAS?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/eaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/eaas/</guid>
      <description>The internet has allowed software to be accessed remotely leading to different kinds of services:&#xA;Software as a service or SaaS: these are software that is accessed over the internet. Examples are Google Docs, HR apps, Online accounting software Platform as a service or PaaS: these are online platforms that allow software or services to be built on them. Examples are Heroku, Engine yard, Appfog Infrastructure as a service or IaaS: these are comupter infrastructure that can be accessed online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pointtax as a Solution to Tax Evasion and Budget Deficits</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/pointtax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/pointtax/</guid>
      <description>Update June 2020: In 2015, our model predicted a huge global crisis starting in 2019 to be felt many years afterwards. This is now known as the Covid-19 pandemic. Our model predicts inflation next, as a result of governments applying sophistical mercantile solutions, now known as &amp;ldquo;bailouts&amp;rdquo;, on supply and demand problems. These bailouts will be paid for by either inflation (as college debt, rising bills, rent, etc) or by increased taxation, both will lead to unrest (as seen in the US riots) or a change in government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presenting: Our marriage app</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/marriage-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/supereconomics/marriage-app/</guid>
      <description>For valentines&amp;rsquo; day, we started prototyping a marriage feature for our social economic system.&#xA;Those who have been following our blog know that the economic aspects of our system is based largely on Adam Smith. But marriage is more fundamental than economics, and so we based our marriage feature instead on Smith&amp;rsquo;s best friend David Hume, who wrote an entire treatise on human nature.&#xA;&amp;lsquo;Of the amorous passions&amp;quot; David Hume described the propensities of human nature that prompt us to fall in love.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
