<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Partners on Pantrypoints</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/partners/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Partners on Pantrypoints</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/partners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Partner: AMSAI E-Learning and AF Organic</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/23-05-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/23-05-06/</guid>
      <description>Last week, we pitched our Pantrypreneur Farm system to Makati Rotary Club but couldn&amp;rsquo;t get any significant reception for the idea.&#xA;So we decided to pause it and focus on Pantrypreneur Educate which was relatively undeveloped.&#xA;By sheer coincidence, we met the lead administrator for AMSAI E-Learning on the same day. She was willing to implement our proposed moneyless tuition system.&#xA;We also partnered with AF Organic, an organic farm in Paranaque, to use exchange points for some of their transactions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Partner: VGE</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/23-04-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/23-04-10/</guid>
      <description>We welcome VGE into the Pantrypoints system.&#xA;VGE stands for Venezuela Gente Excelente, a socio-civic group that aims for a prosperous Venezuela by lobbying peacefully against the oppressive policies of the Maduro regime.&#xA;They will test our points-based system in a small part of their 23 hectare farm in Venezuela in 2024 after we finish our testing in the Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Partners: Unladsaka</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/23-03-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/23-03-04/</guid>
      <description>We welcome Unladsaka and SuperPaso into the Pantrypoints system.&#xA;Unlad Saka is a farmers association based in Quezon City. They will implement Pantrypreneur Farm for rural farms and Village Subsistence Farming for urban farms.&#xA;Super Paso is a maker of home garden planting kits and organic fertilizers. They will give consultation for our Village Subsistence Farming system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Partner: FINAC</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/23-01-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/23-01-28/</guid>
      <description>We welcome FINAC into the Pantrypoints system.&#xA;FINAC stands for Filipino Inventors Advocacy Coooperative, a group that promotes Filipino inventions and their makers.&#xA;They will implement the offline version of the Pantrypoints system, as well as assist in the patenting of the inventions from Pantrypoints and Superphysics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Partners: Himalayan Consultancy</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/22-10-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/22-10-06/</guid>
      <description>We welcome Himalayan Asia Management Consulting Services into our points-based system..&#xA;Himalayan is an geological engineering firm based in Davao Philippines. We met them during the German-Philippines Business Conference on Recycling and Waste Management </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Partners: San Pedro City Agricultural Office and Pacita Organic Garden</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/22-09-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/22-09-16/</guid>
      <description>We welcome more partners implementing our moneyless points system:&#xA;San Pedro City Agricultural Office The San Pedro City Agricultural Office is a part of San Pedro City Government managing the agricultural activities for San Pedro City in Laguna.&#xA;Pacita Organic Garden Pacita Organic Garden is a community of small organic farmers in Pacita Complex, Laguna.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Partner: Capri Island Cafe</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/22-09-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/22-09-06/</guid>
      <description>We welcome more partners implementing our moneyless points system:&#xA;Capri Island Cafe Capri Island is a Vegetarian Cafe and Restaurant that serves sentient, cruelty-free food. They will use Pantrypreneur Rewards for their customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Partners: Ayus and SCENAC</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/22-08-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/22-08-15/</guid>
      <description>We welcome more partners implementing our moneyless points system:&#xA;/graphics/ayus.jpg&#xA;Ayus Ayus is a health store that sells alternative remedies such as those from ayurveda and homoeopathy. They will use trade points for their loyal customers.&#xA;SCENAC SCENAC is a non-goverment organization (NGO) that supports senior citizens. They will test the moneyless social insurance system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Partners: Food Rescue Philippines and Savilas Vietnam</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/22-07-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/22-07-15/</guid>
      <description>We welcome more partners implementing our moneyless points system:&#xA;Food Rescue Philippines Food Rescue Philippines is a volunteer group that uses food waste to end malnutrition and involuntary hunger in the Philippines.&#xA;Savilas Vietnam Savilas is a small seafood company that sources its supplies from sustainable fisheries in Vietnam. We got in touch with them while we were adapting the Pantrypoints system for the Fishackathon challenge earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Partner: Angel&#39;s Shelter</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/22-04-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/22-04-19/</guid>
      <description>We welcome Angel&amp;rsquo;s Shelter to the Pantrypoints System.&#xA;Angel&amp;rsquo;s Shelter is an animal shelter in Binan Laguna, Philippines. They also do food rescue for feeding programs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
